A Guide to the Robert Prentiss Daniel Papers 1920-1966
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Printed
  - Virginia Union University
    - Virginia Union University Bulletin March, 1930 (Box-folder 13:15)
    - Virginia Union University Bulletin November, 1935 (Box-folder 13:16)
    - Virginia Union University Bulletin April, 1936 (Box-folder 13:17)
    - Virginia Union University Bulletin June, 1938 (Box-folder 13:18)
    - Virginia Union University Bulletin November, 1947 (Box-folder 13:19)
    - Virginia Union University Bulletin June 1949 (Box-folder 13:20)
  - Shaw University
    - Inauguration as 5th President November 20, 1936 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Christmas Number December, 1937 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - President's Report September, 1940 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - President's Report Number October, 1941 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Alumni Number May, 1942 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Program of Founder's Day November, 1946 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - The Department of Rural Church March, 1948 (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Homecoming Number October, 1948 (Box-folder 14:8)
    - President's Report Number November, 1948 (Box-folder 14:9)
    - President's Report Number November, 1949 (Box-folder 14:10)
  - The Sphinx
    - The Spinx of Alpha Phi Alpha June 1915 Vol #2 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Xmas Sphinx of Alpha Phi Alpha December 1916 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - The Sphinx October 1916 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - The Sphinx February 1916 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - The Sphinx April 1917 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - The Sphinx Xmas Alumni Issue December 1916 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - The Sphinx April 1917 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - The Sphinx April 1917 (Box-folder 15:8)
    - The Sphinx Quarterly April 1918 (Box-folder 15:9)
    - The Sphinx Convention December 1918 (Box-folder 15:10)
    - The Sphinx Quarterly Carl J. Murphy (Box-folder 15:11)
    - The Sphinx Quarterly June 1919 (Box-folder 15:12)
    - The Sphinx Quarterly December 27th 1919 (Box-folder 15:13)
    - The Sphinx Quarterly Carl J. Murphy Convention December 27th-30th (Box-folder 15:14)
    - The Sphinx Quarterly 12th Annual Convention (Box-folder 15:15)
    - The Sphinx Quarterly May 1920 (Box-folder 15:16)
    - The Sphinx Vol XIII 1927 (Box-folder 15:17)
    - The Sphinx Vol XIV 1928 (Box-folder 15:18)
    - The Sphinx Post War Expansion 1946 (Box-folder 15:19)
    - The Sphinx Convention News February 1921 (Box-folder 15:20)
    - The Sphinx Chapter Elections February 1922 (Box-folder 15:21)
    - The Sphinx Commencement October 1923 (Box-folder 15:22)
    - The Sphinx Convention February 1925 (Box-folder 15:23)
  - Degrees and Appointments
    - Carrie Green, Wayland Seminary 1886 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Charles James daniel, Bluestone Harmony MCMXXXV (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Blanche Ardell Taylor, Armstrong High School January, 1923 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - John Robert Taylor, Armstrong 1931 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - John Robert Taylor, Va Union University 1936 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Robert James Robinson Bachelor of Science 1939 (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Newspapers
    - The Carolina Tribune April 12, 1941 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - The Wilmington Journal August 4, 1951 (Box-folder 17:8)
    - The National Baptist Union Review November 11, 1950 (Box-folder 17:9)
    - The Richmond Afro-American October 21, 1950 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - The Norfolk Journal and Guide February 11, 1950 (Box-folder 17:11)
    - The Boston Chronicle January 11, 1947 (Box-folder 17:12)
    - The Amsterdam News March 3, 1951 (Box-folder 17:13)
    - The Charlottesville Tribune April 28, 1951 (Box-folder 17:14)
    - The Tribune April 18, 1959 (Box-folder 17:15)
  - NewsClippings
    - Newsclippings from a number of newspapers, most are Virginia. (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Civil Rights in Petersburg
    - Political Action Committee Newsletter (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Emergency Mass Meeting June 19, 1960 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - PAC Ruckers's, No Jim Crow (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Citizens Action Meeting Zion Baptist Church (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Citizens Action Bethany Baptist Church (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Citizens Action Tabernacle Baptist Church (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Citizens Protest Meeting Zion Baptist Church (Box-folder 19:7)
- Artifacts
  - Boy Scouts of America in Appreciation (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Michigan State Centennial (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Michigan State College Centennial (Box-folder 20:3)
  - U.S. Army Infantry School (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Faculty and Staff Thank You for Service (Box-folder 20:5)
  - USS George Washington Carver Strentgh Through Knowledge (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha 20th Annual Convention Pin (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha Black and Gold Medal (Box-folder 20:8)
  - African Head Mrs. Ida Stevens January 4, 1965 (Box-folder 20:9)